Binkowski, Don Collection of Leo Krzycki Memorabilia 6353 MB
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Don Binkowski Collection of Leo Krzycki Memorabilia
1916-1983
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Binkowski, Don
Krzycki, Leo
6353 MB
0.83 cubic feet
0.8 linear ft.
Memorabilia, photographs.
8023696
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 27, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Binkowski, Don, 1929-; Krzycki, Leo; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; Amalgamated Lithographers of America. Local 1 (New York); Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.); Federation of Dyers, Finishers, Printers and Bleachers of America; International Union of Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers; International Union, United Automobile Workers of America (CIO); Michigan State Industrial Union Council; United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America; United Rubber Workers of America; United Steelworkers of America
8023696
- Leo Krzycki Badges, 1924-1934 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America
- Leo Krzycki Badges, 1936-1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; Steel Workers Organizing Committee, CIO; CIO; International Union United Automobile Workers of America
- Leo Krzycki Badges, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Federation of Dyers, Finishers Printers & Bleachers of America; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; CIO
- Leo Krzycki Badges, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  CIO; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; United Rubber Workers of America; International Union United Automobile Workers of America
- Leo Krzycki Badges, 1943-1946 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  CIO; United Farm Equipment & Metal Workers of America; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America
- Leo Krzycki Badges, 1947-1960 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  1947-1948, 1950, 1960, unknown. CIO; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; United Steelworkers of America; Amalgamated Lithographers of America
- Assorted pins and badges (Box 1, Folder 7)
  "Our Shirt for Roosevelt"; Krzycki for Congress; United Textile Workers of America; United Farm Equipment & Metal Workers of America
- Photographs and information (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Badges & Buttons (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Michigan Labor Welcomes Mandela Freedom Tour 1990; American Slav Congress United for Victory; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (badge) Biennial Convention, May 1966, Delegate (ribbons are torn and faded); Za-Odre-NYSE-Baltyk (pendant on a blue and white ribbon)
- Michigan CIO Badges, 1944-1955 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Delegate - 10th Convention - UAW-CIO Atlantic City March 23, 1946 (Andrew J. Ignash, LU600 - Dearborn); Delegate - Michigan CIO Council Seventh Annual Convention, July 12-16, 1944 (Andrew J. Ignasiak - #600 UAW Detroit); Visitor - 8th Annual convention Michigan State CIO Council Detroit - June 10-11, 1946; Visitor - June 11,12,13 & 14, 1956, Grand Rapids, Michigan; Guest - First Convention, AFL-CIO - New York City Dec. 5, 1955
- Assorted Badges, 1916-1951 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Alternate Delegate, 7th Annual Convention - UAW CIO - Chicago, Ill. - August 3rd, 1942; Delegate - 17th Constitutional Convention; Polish American Club of So. Manchester, Conn. - Organized 1916; International Rep. - 16th Convention - UAW-CIO, Cleveland, Ohio - April 1-7, 1951; Visitor - Eleventh Annual Convention - Michigan State - CIO Council, Grand Rapids, Mich. - May 23,24,25, 1949
- Convention Ribbons, 1971-1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  112th Annual Convention, State Council of Pennsylvania Jr. Order, United American Mechanics, Easton, PA. - Sept. 16-17, 1971; 117th State Convention Jr. O.U.A.M. - Seven Springs Pennsylvania - Sept. 22,23,24, 1976 (2); 116th Annual Convention Grand Lodge - E.F. Johnson Grand Chancellor - August 22nd-24th, 1983 - Downingtown, PA.; Jr. O.U.A.M. - 128th Annual Session, York, PA 1987; Schilling Adv.; Jr. Order - United American Mechanics - 124th Annual Session - Sheraton Jet-Port - Sept. 15 & 16, 1983; 122nd - State Convention - Jr. O.U.A.M. - Altoona, PA - Sept. 16-18, 1981